National American Woman Suffrage Association Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Subject File, 1851-1953 (Box 37-80, OV 1, Reel 24-58)
  - Leslie Woman Suffrage Commission
    - Litigation
      - 19 of 20 (Box 61, Reel 44)
      - 20 of 20 (Box 62, Reel 44)
    - Index of the minutes
    - Minutes
      - 1 of 3
      - 2 of 3 (Box 63, Reel 45)
      - 3 of 3
    - Miscellany
      - 1 of 5
      - 2 of 5
      - 3 of 5
      - 4 of 5
      - 5 of 5
  - Letterheads (Box 64, Reel 45)
  - The Lily
  - Lindsey, Ben B.
  - Livermore, Mary Ashton Rice
  - Livingston, Rose
  - Lovell, Mary F.
  - Luscomb, Florence H.
  - Lutz, Bertha
  - Lyon, Mary
  - McCulloch, Catharine W.
  - McDowell, Mary E.
  - McKenzie, William P.
  - Maryland suffrage associations
  - Massachusetts Anti-Slavery Society
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Massachusetts suffrage associations (Box 64, Reel 46)
  - May, Abby W.
  - Mead, Lucia Ames
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Medicine, women in (Box 65, Reel 46)
  - Men's leagues for woman suffrage
  - Meredith, Ellis
  - Merrick, Caroline E.
  - Michigan suffrage associations
  - Milholland, Inez
  - Mill, John Stuart
  - Mississippi Valley Suffrage Conference
  - Missouri suffrage associations
  - Mistral, Gabriela
  - Mooney, Tom
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Morris, Esther
  - Mott, Lucretia
  - National Anti-Slavery Standard
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People
  - National Council of Women
  - National Dress Reform Association
  - National League of Women Voters (Box 66, Reel 46)
    - 10th anniversary of woman suffrage, 1927
      - Addresses
      - Memorial fund
      - Minutes, reports
      - Telegrams
    - Convention, 1930
      - Press releases
      - Program changes
      - Resolutions (Box 66, Reel 47)
      - State rolls of honor
      - Treasurer's report
      - Printed matter
    - General
    - Printed matter
  - National Woman Suffrage Association (Box 67, Reel 47)
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - National Woman's Party
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - National Women's Trade Union League
  - Nebraska suffrage associations
  - Needham, Ellie
  - Nevada suffrage associations
  - New England Woman Suffrage Association
  - New England Woman's Press Association
  - New England Woman's Rights Convention
  - New England Women's Club
  - New Hampshire suffrage associations
  - New Jersey suffrage associations (Box 67, Reel 48)
  - New York City Anti-Slavery Society
  - New York Infirmary
  - New York State League of Women Voters
  - New York State suffrage associations (Box 68, Reel 48)
    - General
      - 1 of 5
      - 2 of 5
      - 3 of 5
      - 4 of 5
      - 5 of 5
    - James Wolcott Wadsworth (1877-1952)
  - Newspapers favoring woman suffrage, list of
  - Nightingale, Florence
  - Oberlin College, Oberlin, Ohio
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Ogden, Esther
  - O'Hare, Kate Richards
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Ohio suffrage associations (Box 69, Reel 49)
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Oklahoma suffrage associations
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Oliphant, Laurence
  - Osgood, Fanny C.
  - Page, George H.
  - Palmer, Alice Freeman
  - Pankhurst, Christabel
  - Pankhurst, E. Sylvia
  - Pankhurst, Emmeline
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Papazian, Bertha S.
  - Parades for suffrage
  - Park, Alice
  - Park, Maud Wood
  - Parker, Theodore
  - Parker, Valeria H.
  - Peck, Mary Gray
  - Peckham, Mary C. (Box 70, Reel 49)
  - Pennsylvania suffrage associations
    - 1 of 5
    - 2 of 5
    - 3 of 5 (Box 70, Reel 50)
    - 4 of 5
    - 5 of 5
  - Philippines suffrage associations
    - 1 of 6
    - 2 of 6
    - 3 of 6 (Box 71, Reel 50)
    - 4 of 6
    - 5 of 6
    - 6 of 6
  - Phillips, Wendell
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2 (Box 71, Reel 51)
  - Pillsbury, Parker
  - Pinkham Memorial Fund
  - Piper, Elizabeth B.
  - Political prisoners
  - Porter, Laura H.
  - Powell, Aaron
  - Progress
  - Prohibition and suffrage
  - Publicity
  - Puerto Rico suffrage associations
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Pullan, R. B.
  - Purvis, Robert
  - Rantoul, Lois B.
  - Republican Party
  - Rhode Island suffrage associations (Box 72, Reel 51)
    - 1 of 16
    - 2 of 16
    - 3 of 16
    - 4 of 16
    - 5 of 16
    - 6 of 16
    - 7 of 16
    - 8 of 16 (Box 72, Reel 52)
    - 9 of 16
    - 10 of 16
    - 11 of 16
    - 12 of 16
    - 13 of 16 (Box 73, Reel 52)
    - 14 of 16
    - 15 of 16
    - 16 of 16
  - Ricker, Marilla M.
  - Ripley, Martha G.
  - Rogers, Harriet A.
  - Roosevelt, Theodore
  - Rose, Ernestine L.
  - Russell, Sarah S.
  - Russian Famine Fund
  - Russian women
  - Sangster, Margaret E.
  - Schwimmer, Rosika
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3 (Box 73, Reel 53)
  - Sewall, James E. and Harriet W.
  - Shafroth, John F.
  - Shaw, Anna Howard
    - 1 of 4
    - 2 of 4
    - 3 of 4
    - 4 of 4
  - Shaw, Pauline Agassiz
  - Shuler, Marjorie
  - Sinclair, Upton (Box 74, Reel 53)
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Smith, Abby H. and Julia E.
  - Smith, Gerrit
  - Smith, Lillian
  - Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C.
  - Snowden, Mrs. Philip
  - Social Hygiene Monthly
  - Soviet bonds
  - Spofford, Jane H.
  - Stanton, Elizabeth Cady
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Stassen, Harold E.
  - Stevenson, Katharine A.
  - Stolle, Antonie
  - Stone, Ellen A.
  - Stowe, Harriet Beecher
  - Strong, Anna Louise
  - Strong, Sydney
  - Suffrage editions of newspapers (Box 74, Reel 54)
  - Suffrage map (Box OV 1, Reel 54)
  - Suffrage plays (Box 74, Reel 54)
  - Suffrage schools
  - Suffrage songs (Box 75, Reel 54)
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Sumner, Charles
  - Sunderland, Jabez T.
  - Szold, Henrietta
  - Tallant, Alice W.
  - Tax protests
  - Taylor, Mentia
  - Temperance
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Temperance posters
  - Tennessee suffrage associations
  - Tilton, Elizabeth
    - 1 of 5
    - 2 of 5
    - 3 of 5
    - 4 of 5
    - 5 of 5
  - Townsend, Jessie E. (Box 75, Reel 55)
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Train, George F.
  - Union Française Pour le Suffrage des Femmes (Box 76, Reel 55)
  - United Nations
  - Utah suffrage associations
  - Valentine, Lila M.
  - Van Winkle, Mina
  - Victory, How Women Won It
  - Virginia suffrage associations
  - Vogl, Susan
  - Walker, Mary (Dr.)
  - Wall, Sarah E.
  - Walton, Ann
  - Ward, Joseph
  - Western Anti-Slavery Society
  - Whitehouse, Mrs. Norman
  - Whitman, Mrs. John P.
  - Whitney, Edward
  - Whittier, John Greenleaf
  - Widdrington, Enid
  - Willard, Emma
  - Willard, Frances E.
  - Wilson, Woodrow
    - 1 of 2
    - 1 of 2
  - Wisconsin suffrage associations
  - Wollstonecraft, Mary
  - Woman Citizen
  - Woman suffrage amendment See also Container 53, Equal rights amendment
    - General
      - 1 of 4
      - 2 of 4
      - 3 of 4
      - 4 of 4
    - History (Box 77, Reel 56)
      - 1 of 5
      - 2 of 5
      - 3 of 5
      - 4 of 5
      - 5 of 5
  - The Woman's Bible
  - Woman's Centennial Congress (1940), New York, N.Y.
  - Woman's Column
  - Woman's Journal
    - 1907-1917
    - 1917-1949
    - Account book, 1901-1903
    - State list, 1881 (Box 78, Reel 56)
    - Tour of Europe
    - Subscription list (Box 78, Reel 57)
      - 1887
      - 1892, Feb.-1893, Mar.
      - 1893, Apr.-1894, Sept.
      - 1894, Sept.-1897, Oct.
    - Subscription list, circa 1910 (Box 79, Reel 57)
  - Woman's rights conventions
  - Woman's rights conventions (Box 80, Reel 58)
  - Women's International Organisations
    - Liaison Committee
    - Peace and Disarmament Committee
  - Women's Social and Political Union
  - Woodhull, Victoria C.
  - Wright, Frances
  - Zangwill, Israel
- Miscellany, 1890-1950 (Box 81-98, Reel 58-73)
  Miscellaneous material including reports, speeches, typescripts, photographs, minutes, newspaper clippings, and pamphlets; scrapbooks compiled by Ida Porter Boyer; and printed matter.
  Arranged by type of material and chronologically therein.
  - 1890-1899 (Box 81, Reel 58)
  - 1900
  - 1901
  - 1902
  - 1903
  - 1904
  - 1905
  - 1906
  - 1907
  - 1908
  - 1910-1911
  - 1912
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - 1913
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2 (Box 81, Reel 59)
  - 1914-1915
  - 1916 (Box 82, Reel 59)
    - 1 of 5
    - 2 of 5
    - 3 of 5
    - 4 of 5
    - 5 of 5
  - 1917 (Box 82, Reel 60)
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - 1917 (Box 83, Reel 60)
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - 1918
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - 1919 (Box 84, Reel 61)
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - 1920
  - 1920-1922
  - 1935
  - 1938
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Photographs (Box 85, Reel 61)
  - 1939
  - 1940
  - 1941
  - 1942
  - 1943
  - 1945
  - 1946
  - 1947
  - 1948
  - 1949
  - 1950
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Treasurer's final report, NAWSA, 1950
  - General
  - Ida Porter Boyer scrapbooks (Box 86, Reel 61)
    - Index
    - vol. 1 (Box 86, Reel 62)
    - vol. 2 (Box 87, Reel 62)
    - vol. 3 (Box 88, Reel 63)
    - vol. 4
    - vol. 5 (Box 89, Reel 63)
    - vol. 6 (Box 89, Reel 64)
    - Unbound material
    - vol. 7 (Box 90, Reel 64)
    - vol. 8
  - List of suffrage papers (Box 91, Reel 64)
  - Printed matter
    - 1 of 34
    - 2 of 34
    - 3 of 34
    - 4 of 34
    - 5 of 34
    - 6 of 34 (Box 91, Reel 65)
    - 7 of 34
    - 8 of 34 (Box 92, Reel 65)
    - 9 of 34
    - 10 of 34
    - 11 of 34 (Box 92, Reel 66)
    - 12 of 34
    - 13 of 34
    - 14 of 34
    - 15 of 34
    - 16 of 34
    - 17 of 34
    - 18 of 34 (Box 93, Reel 66)
    - 19 of 34
    - 20 of 34 (Box 93, Reel 67)
    - 21 of 34
    - 22 of 34
    - 23 of 34
    - 24 of 34
    - 25 of 34
    - 26 of 34
    - 27 of 34 (Box 93, Reel 68)
    - 28 of 34
    - 29 of 34
    - 30 of 34
    - 31 of 34
    - 32 of 34
    - 33 of 34
    - 34 of 34 (Box 94, Reel 68)
  - Scrapbooks (2 vols.)
  - Printed matter (Box 94, Reel 69)
    - 1 of 33
    - 2 of 33 (Box 95, Reel 69)
    - 3 of 33
    - 4 of 33
    - 5 of 33
    - 6 of 33
    - 7 of 33 (Box 95, Reel 70)
    - 8 of 33
    - 9 of 33
    - 10 of 33
    - 11 of 33 (Box 96, Reel 70)
    - 12 of 33
    - 13 of 33
    - 14 of 33
    - 15 of 33 (Box 96, Reel 71)
    - 16 of 33
    - 17 of 33
    - 18 of 33
    - 19 of 33 (Box 97, Reel 71)
    - 20 of 33
    - 21 of 33
    - 22 of 33 (Box 97, Reel 72)
    - 23 of 33
    - 24 of 33 (Box 98, Reel 72)
    - 25 of 33
    - 26 of 33
    - 27 of 33 (Box 98, Reel 73)
    - 28 of 33
    - 29 of 33
    - 30 of 33
    - 31 of 33
    - 32 of 33
    - 33 of 33